LUCY CHENG

200 Akmechet Avenue, #100 ~ Darhan, Mongolia 004852 +48-111-222-4444 lccheng@net.net

INTERNATIONAL BANKER

A highly qualified, results-oriented international banker with broad and diversified experience in corporate strategy, project finance, equity investments, bond origination, loan origination, international trade and legislative/regulatory issues. Fluent in German, English and Japanese. Conversant in Russian and Chinese. Comprehensive knowledge of Central Asia. Practiced in Policy Dialogue.

- ◆ Project Implementation ◆ Investment Management ◆ Research/Analysis
- ◆ Risk Management/Analysis ◆ Business Development ◆ Project Management
 - ◆ Negotiation ◆ Financial Management ◆ Due Diligence

SELECTED ACHIEVEMENTS

- Reviewed and analyzed a macro view on the Kazakhstan economy; designed and implemented a country strategy plan selecting projects based on the country's needs.
- Finalized systems and processes on the Grain Receipt Program, which aided in the development of increased market interactions in the grain sector and introduced a new financing instrument to area farmers and banks.
- Spearheaded the implementation of the Grain Receipt Law in Kazakhstan.
- Initiated the Kazakhstan Cooperation Fund, a project totaling EUR 9.3 million that was funded by Japan, Luxembourg and the Netherlands.
- Directed the management of an equity investment to the International Moscow Bank, Moscow, Russian Federation; ensured proper operations and procedures through regular attendance of Board meetings.
- Initiated and facilitated bilateral talks between the Slovak Republic and prospective Japanese investors.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

EUROPEAN BANK, Darhan, Mongolia

2001-Present

An organization developed to aid and build market economies in 27 countries throughout Central Europe and Central Asia; providing financing for industries, banks and businesses.

Associate Banker (2002-Present)

• Manage several critical projects simultaneously, including eight Technical Cooperation Projects in Lebanon totaling EUR 4.4 million, four Transport Sector Projects in Beirut totaling US\$240 million and Financial Sector Projects in Kazakhstan and Mongolia.



LUCY CHENG

Page Two

Senior Analyst, Central Asia Team – Darhan, Olgij and Kazakhstan, (2001-2002)

- Developed and initiated two Financial Sector Projects in Kazakhstan that promoted the organization's Trade Facilitation Programme.
- Represented the organization and served as Chair of the first Darhan Steering Committee.

INDUSTRIAL BANK OF BERLIN, Berlin, Germany

1992-2001

A banking and securities organization providing financial and professional services to industries throughout the world.

Deputy General Manager (1998-2001)

- Negotiated and managed co-financing opportunities for the organization, which led to the successful origination of two Russian Federation transactions.
- Originated the Foreign Direct Investment Mobilization, involving Spain, the Czech Republic, Poland and Prague.

Senior Manager (1997-1998)

 Originated Sovereign bonds in the Samurai Bond market totaling JPY 30 billion and bookran two DM Bonds totaling DM 530 million.

FINANCIAL TOKYO, Tokyo, Japan

1994-1997

The International Finance Department promotes growth and development through organizational advisement and investment.

Country Manager, Germany, Central and Eastern Europe

 Facilitated the initiation of a US\$300 million Syndicated Loan of the National Bank of Hungary and five yen loan transactions for three German Sovereign borrowers in the amount of JPY 23 billion.

JAPAN CORPORATE FINANCIAL, Tokyo, Japan

1992-1994

A financial services corporation dedicated to serving a broad range of corporations/clients throughout the Tokyo area.

Officer, Nihombashi Branch

Managed 30 separate corporations, with funding responsibility totaling JPY 12 billion.

EDUCATION

YOKOHAMA UNIVERSITY, Yokohama, Japan Bachelor of Arts, Economics, 1992







America's #1 Online Resume Builder

With Cover Letters

- Easy-to-use, guides you through step-by-step
- Resume templates, writing samples and tips
- One-click designs for the professional look you want
- Start from scratch or upload your resume



Already have an account?











Phone and Chat Hours: 7 Days a Week 6am to midnight EST



Write a resume - in minutes

Your resume is often your first and only chance to make a great impression on an employer. Managers will scan your resume for just 10 seconds to see if you're right for the job.

That's why your resume needs to be attractive and stand out. It needs to be well-written and highlight your skills to your best advantage.

The problem is most people don't know how to write a great resume and don't have the design skills to make it look professional.

- Our Resume Builder is designed to make resume-writing fast and easy.
- We match you with the right template and, in just one click, you can choose a professional design that will help you win the job.
- Our unique Text Tuner™ allows you to choose from hundreds of expert-written examples - no more writer's block!

Get the "most impressive resume builder on the market today". There's no risk; no obligation. We're so confident that you'll love our resume builder that you can try it for FREE.

According to our partners..."the most impressive resume builder on the market today."

onTargetiobs

YAHOO! hotjobs EmploymentGuide.com

Ret-Temps Joined

Customer Reviews

Job.com

"I was completely unaware of what companies are looking for in a resume. This product helped me word and format my professional resume and the examples were extremely useful. Overall, this is a great product. I would highly recommend these services." - A. Danihels

"This resume tool is so much better than templates - just upload or enter your resume content and you get your choice of designs. It's magical! Anyone can benefit from this tool: from students to executives!" - Belinda Yanda

View more reviews >



